GP going away was a is a big thing for a
lot of people. First thing that I
thought of was, "Wow, what what what's
next?" More importantly for our
customers and our team, what is change
going to be like for them?
We took [music] that back to the team,
tried to understand the skills we had on
staff both for GP and BC, and bridge the
gap [music] so that our GP consultants
could bring our clients through that
journey to BC. That's why we joined the
cross-skill program.
The value of the cross-skill program to
me was [music] getting our team up to
speed without pulling any of the rest of
us out of the loop. We look at the
cross-skill program [music] as not only
a great opportunity for our people, but
as a necessary move for our business. We
have 100 GP customers to [music] move in
4 years, so the cross-skill program is
essential to our growth.
Our consultants jumped into [music] it
right away and have really loved it
since day one. I did not think that the
[music] cross-skill program would be
this easy.
The people that went through the
training [music] are raising their hands
saying that they would like to be
involved. They would like to do this or
that they have these other resources
still available [music] to them. They
want to hit the ground running. Our
people really feel like [music] we're
behind them and supporting them in
telling them, "Hey, we want you to go
through this training [music]
not just, you know, for our own benefit
as a company but for your benefit as
[music] a consultant." There's no reason
not to join the cross-skill program.
Cross-skill program sets up Grayhawk for
success in the future by putting us in
the best position to help our customers
succeed. That's our tagline as a company
is our business is your success.